<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<Entries>
  <Entry>
    <Key>1</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Azimuth</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>2</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Azimuth value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>3</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Note Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>4</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Determines the type of Note to remember.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>5</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Value</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>6</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The value to be remembered.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>7</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>For Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>8</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The ID of the Job for which this Note is remembered. If omitted - ForJob is taken to be the ID of the Job that issued this Remember Command.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>9</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Boolean</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>10</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Boolean value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>11</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Integer</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>12</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Integer value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>13</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Real</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>14</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Real value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>15</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>16</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a String value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>17</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Enumeration</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>18</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Enumeration value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>19</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Time</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>20</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Time value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>21</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Timespan</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>22</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Timespan value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>23</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Current Time</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>24</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) the current time in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>25</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The memory note in which to store the current time.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>26</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Sector</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>27</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Sector value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>28</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Object</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>29</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Object value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>30</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Object Collection</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>31</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Object Collection value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>32</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Point</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>33</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Point value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>34</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Polyline</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>35</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Polyline value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>36</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Polygon</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>37</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Polygon value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>38</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Ellipse</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>39</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Ellipse value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>40</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>41</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Unit value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>42</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Unit Collection</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>43</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Unit Collection value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>44</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Task</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>45</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Task value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>46</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Cluster</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>47</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Cluster value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>48</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Strike Point</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>49</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a StrikePoint value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>50</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Native Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>51</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a NativeType value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>52</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Conditionally Remember String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>53</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) the specified string Value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value, only if there is no active Job in the receiving Unit for which current value of this memory note is a non-null string, otherwise - current value remains as is.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>54</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Ask Enumeration</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>55</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Present a question (typically to a user) and possibly remember (store) the answer (an Enumeration value) in the memory of the receiving Unit, for a Job whose ID is the specified ForJob value - if and when an answer is received.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>56</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Question</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>57</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The phrasing of the question to be presented.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>58</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>On Behalf of</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>59</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Only specified if the question is being asked on behalf of another Unit (typically the commanding Unit). If omitted - the question is considered to be asked by the executing Unit itself.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>60</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Answer Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>61</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The type of Enumeration Value that should be used for providing an answer to the question.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>62</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Answer Note Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>63</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Memory Note in which to remember the answer - if and when it is received.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>64</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The ID of the Job for which the Note containing the answer is remembered. If omitted - ForJob is taken to be the ID of the Job that issued this Ask Command.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>65</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Send Event</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>66</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Send the specified  Event to the specified Recipients.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>67</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Event</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>68</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recipients</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>69</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>End Task</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>70</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Immediately end execution of the containing Task. This command may only be placed inside a Cell, i.e. it may not be used as a Reaction Command in a Reaction Rule.
Note that for iterative Commands, "EndTask" only ends the Task for the current iteration. Successive iterations are completely unaffected. </English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>71</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Azimuth for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>72</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Azimuth value that was previousely remembered (through RememberAzimuth Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - "false" is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>73</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The type of Note to recall.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>74</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>75</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Unit whose memory is checked.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>76</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The ID of the Job for which the recalled Note was remembered.
If a Null Integer is specified - ForJob is considered to be a wildcard, i.e. it doesn't matter for which Job the Note was remembered.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>77</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Boolean for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>78</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Boolean value that was previousely remembered (through RememberBoolean Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - "false" is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>79</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Integer for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>80</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Integer value that was previousely remembered (through RememberInteger Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullInteger is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>81</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Real for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>82</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Real value that was previousely remembered (through RememberReal Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullReal is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>83</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall String for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>84</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a String value that was previousely remembered (through RememberString Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - an empty String is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>85</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Enumeration for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>86</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Enumeration value that was previousely remembered (through RememberEnumeration Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - NullEnumeration is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>87</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Time for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>88</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Time value that was previousely remembered (through RememberTime Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullTime is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>89</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Timespan for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>90</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Timespan value that was previousely remembered (through RememberTimespan Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullTimespan is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>91</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Sector for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>92</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Sector value that was previousely remembered (through RememberSector Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullSector is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>93</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Point for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>94</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Point value that was previousely remembered (through RememberPoint Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullPoint is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>95</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Polyline for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>96</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Polyline value that was previousely remembered (through RememberPolyline Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullPolyline is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>97</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Polygon for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>98</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Polygon value that was previousely remembered (through RememberPolygon Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - an EmptyPolygon is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>99</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Ellipse for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>100</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Ellipse value that was previousely remembered (through RememberEllipse Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullEllipse is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>101</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Unit for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>102</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Unit value that was previousely remembered (through RememberUnit Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullUnit is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>103</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Unit Collection for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>104</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a UnitCollection value that was previousely remembered (through RememberUnitCollection Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullUnitCollection is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>105</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Object for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>106</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Object value that was previousely remembered (through RememberObject Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullObject is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>107</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Object Collection for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>108</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Object Collection value that was previousely remembered (through RememberObjectCollection Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - an EmptyObjectCollection is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>109</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Task for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>110</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Task value that was previousely remembered (through RememberTask Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullTask is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>111</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Cluster for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>112</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Cluster value that was previousely remembered (through RememberCluster Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullCluster is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>113</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Strike Point for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>114</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Strike Point value that was previousely remembered (through RememberStrikePoint Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullStrikePoint is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>115</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Native Type for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>116</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a NativeType value that was previousely remembered (through RememberNativeType Atomic Command) in the specified Unit for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer).
If the specified NoteType was not previously remembered in the specified Unit for that Job - a NullNativeType is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>117</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Boolean for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>118</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns all Units found in the specified Subjects collection, whose memory contains the specified NoteValue for the specified NoteType, remembered for a Job with the specified ForJob ID (for any Job if ForJob equals Null Integer), i.e. all Units Ui for which Recall(NoteType,Ui,ForJob) = NoteValue.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>119</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Subjects</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>120</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Units whose memory repositories are inspected.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>121</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The type of Note to look for.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>122</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Note Value</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>123</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The value to look for.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>124</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The ID of the Job for which the Note was remembered.
If a Null Integer is specified - ForJob is considered to be a wildcard, i.e. it doesn't matter for which Job the Note was remembered.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>125</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Integer for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>126</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Unit for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>127</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering String for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>128</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Object for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>129</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Time for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>130</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Units Remembering Enumeration for Job</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>131</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>132</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Unit for which the Doctrinal Command/Reaction Rule is being planned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>133</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Job ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>134</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Job ID that is associated with the Doctrinal Command being planned. If the Doctrinal Command is not associated with any Job ID - a NullInteger is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>135</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Task Leaders</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>136</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a the top Units ("Leaders") assigned to all instances of the specified Task whose instance index (1-based) is between the specified FromInstance and ToInstance.
Relevant for Doctrinal Commands only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>137</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Task</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>138</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>From Instance</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>139</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>To Instance</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>140</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Task Leaf Units</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>141</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns all lower level Units ("leaves" of the OrBat tree) assigned to all instances of the specified Task whose instance index (1-based) is between the specified FromInstance and ToInstance.
Relevant for Doctrinal Commands only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>142</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Start Location</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>143</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Start Location defined for the planned Doctrinal Command/Reaction Rule.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>144</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Current Iteration Number</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>145</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the sequence number (1-based) of the current iteration of the planned Doctrinal Command.
Relevant for Iterative Doctrinal Commands only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>146</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Current Task Instance</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>147</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Instance index (1-based) of the currently planned Task.
Relevant for Doctrinal Commands only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>148</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Candidate Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>149</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Unit currently considered (by the Manning Algorithm) as a candidate for the containing Manning Element.
This Function may only be used in a Condition Expression and Suitability Grade Expression of a Manning Element.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>150</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Start Time</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>151</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Start Time defined for the planned Doctrinal Command/Reaction Rule.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>152</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Event Sender</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>153</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Unit that sent the Event that triggered the Reaction Rule.
Relevant for Reaction Rules only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>154</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Deferred Execution</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>155</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns 'true' if the Command being validated is not intended for immediate execution (e.g. a Command that belongs to a manually edited Plan (GNT)).
Relevant for Validation Conditions only.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>156</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>And</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>157</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns "true" if both Boolean1 parameter and Boolean2 parameter are "true".</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>158</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Boolean1</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>159</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Boolean2</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>160</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Or</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>161</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns "true" if Boolean1 parameter is "true" or if Boolean2 parameter is "true", and "false" if both parameters are "false".</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>162</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Integer</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>163</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the WhenTrue parameter if the Condition parameter is true, and the WhenFalse parameter if the Condition is false.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>164</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Condition</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>165</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>WhenTrue</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>166</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>When False</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>167</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Real</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>168</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>169</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Enumeration</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>170</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Timespan</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>171</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Sector</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>172</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Azimuth</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>173</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Point</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>174</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Line</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>175</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Polyline</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>176</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Polygon</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>177</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Ellipse</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>178</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>179</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>When True</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>180</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Unit Collection</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>181</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Cluster</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>182</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Strike Point</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>183</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Time</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>184</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Object</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>185</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Object Collection</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>186</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Native Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>187</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>If Allocation Collection</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>188</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Cell Instance Execution State</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>189</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the current execution state of the specified Cell (indicated by the specified Task, Instance index (1-based) and Phase) in the currently executed Doctrinal Command.
If a Cell of the specified Task, Instance index and Phase does not exist in the currently executed Doctrinal Command - NullEnumeration is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>190</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Instance</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>191</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Phase</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>192</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Topmost Non-Instant Active Job ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>193</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the Job ID of the topmost non-instant active Job in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated).
If no such Job is found - a NullInteger is returned.
Notes:
- A topmost Job is a Job that was not issued by any other Job within the Unit.
- A non-instant Job is a Job whose GNT is non-instant, i.e. has a CDUR_Finite or CDUR_Infinite Duration.
- An active Job is a Job whose Execution State is either ES_Executing or ES_Suspended.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>194</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>SingleTaskOfJob</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>195</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the [Single] Task of the Job of the specified Job ID - provided that it is indeed a Single-Task Job.
If no such Job exists in TheUnit or if that Job is a Multi-Task Job - a NullTask is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>196</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Job ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>197</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Last Issued Command Index</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>198</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the index (1-based) of the Command that was last issued by the specified Task of the [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated).
A NullInteger is returned in the following cases:
- A Job of the specified JobID is not present in TheUnit.
- The [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID does not contain the specified Task.
- The specified Task has not issued any Commands yet.
Note: the indexing of Commands in a Task is continuous, disregarding Phases (division of Commands into Cells).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>199</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Last Command Index</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>200</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the index (1-based) of the last Command in the specified Task of the [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated), that satisfies the following conditions:
- Its index is not lower than the specified StartIndex.
- If the specified CommandID is not empty (Null String) - Its InternalID is the specified CommandID (i.e. an empty CommandID effectively means "don't care" for InternalID).
A NullInteger is returned in the following cases:
- A Job of the specified JobID is not present in TheUnit.
- The [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID does not contain the specified Task.
- The specified Task does not contain a Command that satisfies the abovementioned coditions.
Note: the indexing of Commands in a Task is continuous, disregarding Phases (division of Commands into Cells).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>201</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Start Index</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>202</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Command ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>203</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Command Index By Parameter Value Bool</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>204</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the index (1-based) of the first Command in the specified Task of the [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated), that satisfies the following conditions:
- Its index is not lower than the specified StartIndex.
- Its InternalID is the specified CommandID.
- It has a [Boolean] Parameter whose InternalID is the specified ParameterID and whose value is the specified ParameterValue.
A NullInteger is returned in the following cases:
- A Job of the specified JobID is not present in TheUnit.
- The [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID does not contain the specified Task.
- The specifeid Task does not contain a Command that satisfies the abovementioned coditions.
Note: the indexing of Commands in a Task is continuous, disregarding Phases (division of Commands into Cells).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>205</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Parameter ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>206</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Parameter Value</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>207</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Command Parameter Value Point</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>208</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the value of the Command Parameter that satisfies the following conditions:
- It is a parameter of the Command that is located in the specified CommandIndex (1-based) within the specified Task of the [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated).
- Its InternalID is the specified ParameterID.
- It is of type Point.
If no such Command Parameter is found - a NullPoint is returned.
Note: the indexing of Commands in a Task is continuous, disregarding Phases (division of Commands into Cells).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>209</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Command Index</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>210</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Command Parameter Value Object</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>211</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the value of the Command Parameter that satisfies the following conditions:
- It is a parameter of the Command that is located in the specified CommandIndex (1-based) within the specified Task of the [GNT of the] Job of the specified JobID in TheUnit (the Unit in which the Function is being evaluated).
- Its InternalID is the specified ParameterID.
- It is of type Object.
If no such Command Parameter is found - a NullObject is returned.
Note: the indexing of Commands in a Task is continuous, disregarding Phases (division of Commands into Cells).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>212</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>213</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns 'true' during Dry Running (both planning and execution).
Note: "Dry Running" a Doctrinal Command/GNT is a process of executing it without consuming time and without influencing the simulated world, i.e without issuing any Atomic Command that may change it.
"Dry Running" is the equivalent of "imagining" execution for the purpose of gaining insight into the expected outcome - in the form of generated Overlay Elements an/or remembered Memory Notes.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>214</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Dry Run Memory ID</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>215</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a nonexistent Job ID that is used as a ForJob value for Remember-ing and Recall-ing "Dry Permanent" Memory Notes, that are effectively permanent (retained between Jobs) throughout a single Dry Run but forgotten after it is finished (as they no longer serve any purpose).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>216</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Azimuth as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>217</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns the raw String representation of the specified Value, as used for internal logging (useful for debug purposes).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>218</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Bool as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>219</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Integer as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>220</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Real as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>221</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>String as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>222</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Enumeration as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>223</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Time as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>224</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Timespan as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>225</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Sector as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>226</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Point as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>227</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Line as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>228</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Polyline as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>229</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Polygon as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>230</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Ellipse as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>231</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Unit as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>232</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Unit Collection as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>233</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Object as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>234</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Object Collection as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>235</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Allocation as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>236</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Allocation Collection as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>237</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Task as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>238</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Phase as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>239</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Cluster as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>240</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Cluster Collection as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>241</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Strike Point as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>242</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Native Type as Raw String</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
</Entries>
