<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<Entries>
  <Entry>
    <Key>1</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Azimuth For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>2</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Azimuth value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>3</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Note Type</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>4</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Determines the type of Note to remember.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>5</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Value</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>6</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The value to be remembered.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>7</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>כל היחידה</Hebrew>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>8</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Boolean For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>9</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Boolean value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>10</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Enumeration For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>11</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Enumeration value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>12</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Integer For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>13</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Integer value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>14</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Real For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>15</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) an Real value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>16</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Point For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>17</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Point value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>18</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Polygon For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>19</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Polygon value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>20</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Unit For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>21</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Unit value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>22</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Time For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>23</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Time value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>24</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Timespan For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>25</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Timespan value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>26</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember String For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>27</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a String value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>28</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Object For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>29</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Object value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>30</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Polyline For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>31</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a Polyline value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>32</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember Native Type For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>33</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Remember (store) a NativeType value in the memory of the receiving Unit under the specified Note Type, for the duration of the current Dry Run.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>34</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Azimuth For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>35</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Azimuth value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberAzimuthForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Azimuth is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>36</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>37</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>The Unit whose memory is checked.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>38</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Boolean For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>39</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Boolean value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberBooleanForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit - 'false' is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>40</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Enumeration For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>41</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Enumeration value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberEnumerationForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Enumeration is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>42</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Integer For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>43</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Integer value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberIntegerForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Integer is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>44</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Real For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>45</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Real value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberRealForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Real is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>46</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Point For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>47</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Point value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberPointForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Point is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>48</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Polygon For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>49</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Polygon value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberPolygonForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Polygon is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>50</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Unit For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>51</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Unit value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberUnitForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Unit is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>52</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Time For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>53</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Time value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberTimeForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Time is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>54</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Timespan For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>55</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Timespan value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberTimespanForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Timespan is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>56</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall String For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>57</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a String value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberStringForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null String is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>58</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Object For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>59</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns an Object value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberObjectForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Object is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>60</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Polyline For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>61</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a Polyline value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberPolylineForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null Polyline is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>62</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Recall Native Type For Dry Run</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>63</Key>
    <Value>
      <English>Returns a NativeType value that was previousely remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note (see RememberNativeTypeForDryRun Doctrinal Command).
If the specified NoteType was not remembered in the specified Unit as a Dry Run Note - Null NativeType is returned.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
</Entries>
