<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<Entries>
  <Entry>
    <Key>1</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>הגעה לנקודה על המסלול שנקבע (צק"פ)</Hebrew>
      <English>Arrival at a point on the determined route (company combat team)</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>2</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>הגעה של צק"פ לנקודת יעד על המסלול שנקבע קודם לכן ונשמר בזכרון היחידה, כאשר הנקודה מוגדרת אבסולוטית.
במהלך התנועה מופעלים כללי תגובה לטיפול באירועים הבאים:
- התקלות ביחידות אויב.
- התקלות במכשול על מסלול התנועה.</Hebrew>
      <English>Arrival of a company combat team at a target point on the previously determined route which is stored in the unit's memory, where the point is defined absolutely.
During the movement, response rules are activated to handle the following events:
- Encounters with enemy units.
- Encounters with an obstacle on the movement route.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>3</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>מפתח הפקודה</Hebrew>
      <English>Command key</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>4</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>נקודת היעד (על המסלול)</Hebrew>
      <English>Target point (on the route)</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>5</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>אופן התנועה</Hebrew>
      <English>Movement mode</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>6</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>בהתקלות</Hebrew>
      <English>On encounter</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>7</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>מעבר בשטח בנוי</Hebrew>
      <English>Passing through a built-up area</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>8</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>תנועה על צירים</Hebrew>
      <English>Movement on axes</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>9</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>הסתר מיחידות אויב</Hebrew>
      <English>Hide from enemy units</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>10</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>סגנון תנועה</Hebrew>
      <English>Movement style</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>11</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>מהירות</Hebrew>
      <English>Speed</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>12</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>המהירות המירבית מתוך המקסימום האפשרי על בסיס הנתונים (בקילומטר לשעה).</Hebrew>
      <English>The maximum speed out of the possible maximum based on the data (in kilometers per hour).</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>13</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>כל היחידה</Hebrew>
      <English>Entire unit</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>14</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>הגעת יח' משנה לנקודה על המסלול שנקבע.
במקרה של התקלות באויב או במכשול על מסלול התנועה מופעלים כללי תגובה מתאימים.</Hebrew>
      <English>Arrival of a sub-unit at a point on the determined route.
In case of an encounter with an enemy or an obstacle on the movement route, appropriate response rules are activated.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>15</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>תחת הגעה לנקודה על המסלול שנקבע (צק"פ)</Hebrew>
      <English>Under arrival at a point on the determined route (company combat team)</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>16</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>האם קב' האמל"ח המצוינת משתתפת בביצוע פקודת "הגעה לנקודה על המסלול שנקבע (צק"פ)" ע"י הפלוגה הממונה שלה.</Hebrew>
      <English>Does the specified ammunition group participate in the execution of the "arrival at a point on the determined route (company combat team)" command by its commanding company.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>17</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>קב' אמל"ח</Hebrew>
      <English>Ammunition group</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>18</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>כל התנאים הבאים מתקיימים:
- הפלוגה הממונה מבצעת פקודת הגעה לנקודה על המסלול שנקבע (צק"פ).
- קב' האמל"ח מבצעת פקודת תנועה בתבנית, בעלת מפתח פקודה Kj.
- הפלוגה הממונה מבצעת פקודת תנועה בתבנית בעלת אותו מפתח פקודה Kj.</Hebrew>
      <English>All the following conditions are met:
- The commanding company is executing an arrival at a point on the determined route (company combat team) command.
- The ammunition group is executing a movement in formation command, with a command key Kj.
- The commanding company is executing a movement in formation command with the same command key Kj.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
  <Entry>
    <Key>19</Key>
    <Value>
      <Hebrew>הסבר: הפלוגה הממונה עשויה לטפל במקביל בביצוע של מספר פקודות תנועה בתבנית - אחת פעילה והשאר בהשעיה זמנית. לכל אחת מהן נשמר בפלוגה מפתח פקודה שונה Ki עבור הג'וב Ki.
קב האמל"ח לעומת זאת עשויה להשתתף בביצוע פקודת תנועה בתבנית אחת לכל היותר.</Hebrew>
      <English>Explanation: The commanding company may be handling the execution of several movement in formation commands in parallel - one active and the rest temporarily suspended. For each of them, a different command key Ki for the job Ki is stored in the company.
The ammunition group, on the other hand, may participate in the execution of at most one movement in formation command.</English>
    </Value>
  </Entry>
</Entries>
